A Guide to the General Assembly Code Revision Vouchers and Distribution Lists, 1811-1850
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
General Assembly Code Revision Vouchers and Distribution Lists, 1811-1850
The Library of Virginia
APA 286, APA 286a
2 folders (50 items, 1 volume)
Auditor of Public Accounts
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by the Auditor of Public Accounts
Historical Information
APA 286: The General Assembly authorized revisions of the Code in 1817, 1819, 1841, 1844, 1846, and 1847. This series consists of vouchers for expenses incurred by officers of the General Assembly in revising and publishing the Code.
APA 286a: Distribution lists from 1811-1822 of various publications, including Acts of the General Assembly, Hening's Statutes at Large, revised Code of Virginia, decisions in General Court, Debates of Convention, Duane's Handbook of Infantry. The publications were delivered to the county clerks of court within the six circuits by "law-carriers". The circuits loosely correspond to the Superior Court of Chancery Districts.
Scope and Content
APA 286: The vouchers include the names of persons to whom money was owed, the amounts, and the dates the vouchers were submitted. Items cover the following dates: 1817, 1819, 1841, and 1846-1850.
APA 286a: The distribution lists indicate the number of copies of the various publications distributed, and the county to which they were delivered. The names of the law-carriers for each circuit are included, as are the names of some of the county clerks who received them.
Contents List
- Code Revision Vouchers, 1817-1850., Extent: 50 items. (Folder 1)
  Chronological
  - Vouchers, 1817.
  - Vouchers, 1819.
  - Vouchers, 1841.
  - Vouchers, 1846.
  - Vouchers, 1847.
  - Vouchers, 1848.
  - Vouchers, 1849.
  - Vouchers, 1850.
- Code Revision Distribution Lists, 1811-1822., Extent: 1 volume (Folder 1)
  - Distribution List, 1811-1822.